Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 3. Phonograph Records, 1906-2003
    - Vinyl, 1946-2003
      - 12" Vinyl, 1946-2001
        - Violin Concerto, 1958; SR-26081; Heifetz, Jascha; Reiner, Fritz; Chicago Symphony Orchestra, The; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2129
        - Serenada Opus 8 / Duo For Violin And Cello, 1961; SR-26082; Heifetz, Jascha; Primrose, William; Piatigorsky, Gregor; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2550
        - Singersâ¦Talkersâ¦Playersâ¦Swingersâ¦ and Doers, 1968; SR-26406; Hellers, The; Command Records (Box 71)
          RS 934 SD
        - Le Voyage, 1968; SR-26407; Henry, Pierre; Limelight; Mercury Records (Box 71)
          LS 86049
        - Honeymoon in Hawaii, 1960; SR-25933; Hilo Hawaiians, The; Hawaii Hosts (Box 4)
          HH 1960
        - Honeymoon in Hawaii, 1960; SR-26035; Hilo Hawaiians, The; Hawaii Hosts (Box 6)
        - Hirt Plays Bert Kaempfert, 1968; SR-26106; Hirt, Al; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LSP-3917
        - Horowitz Plays Chopin, 1957; SR-25928; Horowitz, Vladimir; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 4)
          LM-2137
        - Galactic Fantasy - Eastern Reflections, 1979; SR-26410; Hoskins, William; Spectrum Records (Box 71)
          SR-106
        - Hot Butter, 1973; SR-26169; Musicor Records (Box 44)
          MS 3254
        - Moog: The Electric Eclectics of Dick Hyman, 1969; SR-26166; Hyman, Dick; Command Records (Box 44)
          938-S
        - Moog: The Electric Eclectics of Dick Hyman, 1969; SR-26237; Hyman, Dick; Command Records (Box 45)
        - The Age of Electronicus, 1969; SR-26195; Hyman, Dick; Command Records (Box 45)
          946-S
        - The Age of Electronicus, 1969; SR-26408; Hyman, Dick; Command Records (Box 71)
        - The Age of Electronicus, 1969; SR-26409; Hyman, Dick; Command Records (Box 71)
        - Oasis, 1978; SR-25935; Il Guardiano del Faro; Cetra (Box 4)
          LPX 66
        - Amore Grande Amore Libero, 1975; SR-25934; Il Guardiano del Faro; RCA (Box 4)
          TPL1-1156
        - Oh, Yeah?, 1976; SR-26207; Jan Hammer Group; Nemperor Records (Box 45)
          NE 437
        - Doctor Zhivago Original Sound Track Album, 1965; SR-25936; Jarre, Maurice; MGM Records (Box 4)
          S1E-6ST
        - The Magic Music of Far Away Places, 1965; SR-25937; Kaempfert, Bert; Decca Records (Box 4)
          DL-74616
        - Bye Bye Blues, 1965; SR-25938; Kaempfert, Bert, and His Orchestra; Decca Records (Box 4)
          DL 74963
        - Introducción Critica Jacobo Roman, 1969; SR-25939; Kagel, Mauricio; Discos Soglo Veinte (Box 4)
          JJ 015
        - Kapelle Heirassa, 1967; SR-25940; Pick (Box 4)
          Pick 93-031
        - Instant Production Music, Volume 13: Mostly Jazz, 1979; SR-25941; Karr, Dave; Electrosonic Studio (Box 4)
        - Hawaii's Golden Voice, Undated; SR-25942; Kekaula, Eddie; Kekaula Productions (Box 4)
          KPL-1001
        - A Self-Portrait, 1964; SR-26083-26084; Kennedy, John F.; Caedmon Records (Box 12)
          TC-2021
        - The Pandemonium, 1994; SR-25943; Killing Joke; Butterfly Records (Box 4)
          KJPRO3
        - Shabbat For Today, 1969; SR-26401; Kingsley, Gershon; KNL Records (Box 71)
          LP-GK-2686
        - Gershwin (Alive & Well & Underground), 1970; SR-20803; Kingsley, Gershon; Hambro, Leonid; AVCO Embassy (Box 71)
          AVE 33021
        - Symphony No. 3 In E Flat Major Op. 55 "Eroica", 1961; SR-25944; Klemperer, Otto; Philharmonic Orchestra; Angel Records (Box 4)
          36853
        - Symphony No. 5, 1960; SR-25945; Klemperer, Otto; Philharmonic Orchestra; Angel Records (Box 4)
        - John Cage & Marcel Duchamp, 1977; SR-26268; Knaack, Donald; Finnadar Records (Box 46)
          SR 9017
        - Instant Production Music, Volume 7 - Guitar, 1977; SR-26216; Knight, Lonnie; University Of Wisconsin-Extension (Box 45)
          S80-1456
        - Instant Production Music, Volume 11 - Guitar, 1978; SR-26215; Knight, Lonnie, and Friends; University Of Wisconsin-Extension (Box 45)
          S80-1602
        - Gypsy Passion, 1960; SR-26108; Kostelanetz, Andre; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          CS 8228
        - Kostelanetz Conducts Romantic Waltzes By Tchaikovsky, 1965; SR-26107; Kostelanetz, Andre; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          MS 6824
        - Warsaw Concerto, 1968; SR-26085; Kostelanetz, Andre; Davis, Ivan; Columbia Records (Box 12)
          ML 6226/ MS 6826
        - World Favorite Romantic Concertos For Piano And Orchestra, 1963; SR-26109; Kostelanetz, Andre, and His Orchestra; Davis, Ivan; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          MS 6476
        - Where is Love?, 1974; SR-25946; Kral, Irene; Choice Records (Box 4)
          CRS 1012
        - Gentle Rain, 1978; SR-25947; Kral, Irene; Broadbent, Alan; Choice Records (Box 4)
          CRS 1020
        - The Electric Zodiac, 1969; SR-26191; Leedy, Douglas; Capitol Records (Box 45)
          ST-368
        - An Evening with Tom Lehrer, 1959; SR-25948; Lehrer, Tom; Lehrer Records (Box 4)
          TL 202
        - That Was the Year That Was, 1965; SR-25949; Lehrer, Tom; Reprise Records (Box 5)
          R-6179
        - Invitation To German Poetry, 1959; SR-26086; Lenya, Lotte; Dover Publications (Box 12)
          IGP1
        - The Balinese Gamelan: Music From The Morning Of The World, 1967; SR-25950; Lewiston, David; Nonesuch Records (Box 5)
          H-72015
        - Candlelight Melodies, 1967; SR-25951; Liberace; Longines Symphonette Society (Box 5)
          LWPM 901
        - Dancing Room Only, 1959; SR-25954; Lombardo, Guy, and his Royal Canadians; Capitol Records (Box 5)
          ST1121
        - The Sweetest Sounds Today!, 1967; SR-26110; Lombardo, Guy, and his Royal Canadians; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          ST 2639
        - Dance Medley Time, 1980; SR-25952; Lombardo, Guy, and his Royal Canadians; Decca Records (Box 5)
          DL 74735
        - Guy Lombardo's Greatest Hits, 1966; SR-25953; Lombardo, Guy, and his Royal Canadians; Decca Records (Box 5)
          DL 74812
        - The Louisville Orchestra, 1955; SR-25955; Louisville Orchestra, The; First Edition Records (Box 5)
          LOU-545-5
        - The Louisville Orchestra, 1955; SR-25956; Louisville Orchestra, The; First Edition Records (Box 5)
        - Black Mass, 1971; SR-26210; Lucifer; MCA Records (Box 45)
          Sample copy; 73111
        - Tellus / Fågel Blå, 1969; SR-25957; Lundsten, Ralph; Nilson, Leo; Telestar (Box 5)
          TRS 11066
        - Birds of Fire, 1973; SR-26269; Mahavishnu Orchestra; Columbia Records (Box 46)
          KC 31996
        - Highlights from Il Trovatore, Undated; SR-26111; Mancini, Caterina; Pirazzini, Miriam; Lauri-Volpi, Giacomo; Tagliabue, Carlo; Colella, Alfredo; Orchestra and Chorus of Radio Italiana; Previtali, Fernando; Cetra (Box 19)
          A-50153
        - Mantovani Magic, 1966; SR-26114; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 19)
          PS 448
        - Mantovani Plays The Immortal Classics, 1956; SR-26116; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 19)
          LL 877
        - Mantovani's Golden Hits, 1967; SR-25960; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 5)
          LL 3483
        - Romantic Melodies: An Album Of Favourite Melodies, 1954; SR-26115; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 19)
          LL 979
        - Strauss Waltzes, 1958; SR-25961; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 5)
          PS 118
        - Tango, 1967; SR-25963; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 5)
          PS 532
        - The Music of Victor Herbert and Sigmund Romberg, 1959; SR-25962; Mantovani and His Orchestra; London Records (Box 5)
          PS 165
        - Mariano And The Unbelievables, 1968; SR-26087; Capitol Records (Box 12)
          ST 2831
        - Rock and Other Four Letter Words, 1968; SR-25958; Marks, J.; Lebzelter, Shipen; Columbia Records (Box 5)
          MS 7193
        - Swiss Movement, 1969; SR-26223; McCann, Les; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1537
        - Electronic Music from the Outside In, 1980; SR-25959, 26038; McLean, Barton; McLean, Priscilla; Hanlon, Kevin; Holmes, Reed; Folkways Records (Box 5)
          FPX 6050
        - Moods In Music: Music For Reading, 1952; SR-26112; Melachrino Strings, The; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LPM-1002
        - Verdi - Rigoletto (Highlights), 1965; SR-26088; Merrill, Robert; Moffo, Anna; Kraus, Alfredo; Elias, Rosalind; Flagello, Ezio; Solti, Georg; RCA Italiana Opera Orchestra and Chorus; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2837
        - Look Deeply Into the Mirror, 1973; SR-26150; Michael Quatro Jam Band; Evolution; Stereo Dimensions, Inc. (Box 44)
          Stereo 3021
        - Everything You Always Wanted to Hear on the Moog, 1967; SR-26170; Mighty Moog, The; Columbia Records (Box 44)
          M 30383
        - Great Hits, 1958; SR-25964; Mills Bros., The; Dot Records (Box 5)
          DLP 25157
        - Bose Salutes The Sound Of Mercury Records, 1970; SR-20800; Minneapolis Symphony Orchestra; London Symphony Orchestra; Eastman Wind Ensemble; Eastman Rochester Orchestra; Mercury Records (Box 71)
        - Remarkable Rubin, 1967; SR-26113; Mitchell, Rubin; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          T 2735
        - Moog Power, 1969; SR-26173; Montenegro, Hugo; RCA Records (Box 44)
          LSP-4170
        - Moog Power, 1969; SR-26240; Montenegro, Hugo; RCA Records (Box 46)
        - Beethoven: Symphony No. 2 in D, Op. 36, Undated; SR-25965; Monteux, Pierre; San Francisco Symphony Orchestra; RCA Victor (Box 5)
          LM-1024
        - Christmas Becomes Electric, 1969; SR-20805; Moog Machine, The; Columbia Records (Box 71)
          CS 9959
        - Switched-On Rock, 1969; SR-26171; Moog Machine, The; Columbia Records (Box 44)
          CS 9921
        - Future Memories II, 1984; SR-26273; Moraz, Patrick; Carrere (Box 46)
          66.216
        - The Story Of i, 1976; SR-26274; Moraz, Patrick; Charisma Records Ltd. (Box 46)
          CDS 4002
        - Sings the Great Golden Hits, 1961; SR-25966; Morgan, Jane; Kapp Records (Box 5)
          KS-3246
        - Up North, 1960; SR-26117; Morgan, Jaye P.; MGM Records (Box 19)
          SE3830
        - Symphonie Fantastique, 1962; SR-26227; Munch, Charles; Boston Symphony Orchestra; RCA Victor (Box 45)
          LSC-2608
        - Blues Current, 1970; SR-26272; Murtaugh, John; Polydor Records (Box 46)
          24-4016
        - Spectrum: New American Music, Volume I, 1969; SR-26154; Myrow, Fredric; Reynolds, Roger; Nonesuch Records (Box 44)
          H-71219
        - Recycled, 1975; SR-26151; Nektar; Bellaphon Records (Box 44)
          PPSD-98011; test pressing
        - Hail The Conquering Nero, 1963; SR-26118; Nero, Peter; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LSP-2638
        - Peter Nero Plays Love Is Blue, 1968; SR-26119; Nero, Peter; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LSP-3936
        - Plays a Salute to Herb Alpert and Tijuana Brass, 1967; SR-25967; Nero, Peter; RCA Victor (Box 5)
          LSP-3720
        - Switched on Beatles, 1974; SR-26183; New World Electronic Chamber Ensemble; Mushroom Records (Box 44)
          MRS 5003
        - A Festival Of Famous Conductors: Honoring The 125th Anniversary Of The New York Philharmonic, 1967; SR-25968; New York Philharmonic; Columbia Records (Box 5)
          BM 13
        - Mozart, 1956; SR-25969; Oistrakh, David; Makarov, Abram; Colosseum (Box 5)
          CRLP 194
        - Extended Voices, 1967; Oliveros, Pauline; Lucier, Alvin; Cage, John; Ashely, Robert; Ichiyanagi, Toshi; Feldman, Morton; Odyssey; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 46)
          32 16 0155
        - The Original Trinidad Steel Band, 1977; SR-26120; Original Trinidad Steel Band, The; Elektra Records (Box 19)
          EKS 7139
        - The Blue Danube, 1960; SR-26122; Ormandy, Eugene; Philadelphia Orchestra, The; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          MS 6217
        - The Strings Of The Philadelphia Orchestra, 1957; SR-26121; Ormandy, Eugene; Philadelphia Orchestra, The; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          ML 5187
        - Bridge Over Troubled Water, 1971; SR-25970; Owens, Buck, and His Buckaroos; Capitol Records (Box 5)
          ST-685
        - Delusion Of The Fury - A Ritual Of Dream And Delusion, 1971; SR-26243-26245; Partch, Harry; Columbia Records (Box 46)
          M2 30576
        - Jan Peerce Sings Hebrew Melodies, 1961; SR-25971; Peerce, Jan; RCA Victor (Box 5)
          LSC-2498
        - Spotlight On The Moog - Kaleidoscopic Vibrations, 1971; SR-26160; Perrey & Kingsley; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 44)
          VSD-6525
        - Spotlight On The Moog - Kaleidoscopic Vibrations, 1971; SR-26161; Perrey & Kingsley; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 44)
        - The Amazing New Electronic Pop Sound Of Jean Jacques Perrey, 1968; SR-26271; Perrey, Jean Jacques; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 46)
          VSD-79286
        - Moog Indigo, 1970; SR-26174; Perry, Jean Jacques; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 44)
          VSD-6549
        - Moog Indigo, 1970; SR-26204; Perry, Jean Jacques; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 45)
        - Electronomusic â 9 Images, 1968; SR-26148; Pfeiffer, John; RCA Victrola (Box 44)
          VICS-1371
        - Electronomusic â 9 Images, 1968; SR-26270; Pfeiffer, John; RCA Victrola (Box 46)
        - Gaîté Parisienne - Les Sylphides, 1955; SR-25972; Philadelphia Orchestra, The; Ormandy, Eugene; Columbia Records (Box 5)
          CL 741
        - Instant Production Music Volume Three, 1976; SR-26146; Pilhofer, Herb; University Of Wisconsin-Extension (Box 44)
        - Instant Production Music, Volume 6 - Music from "Earplay", 1977; SR-26217; Pilhofer, Herb; University Of Wisconsin-Extension (Box 45)
          S80-1440
        - King Kong: Jean-Luc Ponty Plays the Music of Frank Zappa, 1970; SR-25973; Ponty, Jean-Luc; World Pacific Jazz (Box 5)
          ST-20172
        - Affenstunde, 1970; SR-26276; Popol VuhÂ â; Liberty Records (Box 46)
          LBS 83 460 I
        - In Den Gärten Pharaos, 1971; SR-26275; Popol VuhÂ â; Pilz (Box 46)
          20 21276-9
        - Roseland NYC Live, 1998; SR-26123-26124; Portishead; Go! Beat (Box 19)
          559 424-1
        - Cosmic Furnace, 1973; SR-26277; Powell, Roger; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 46)
          SD 7241
        - Highlights From Madama Butterfly, 1965; SR-26089; Price, Leontyne; Tucker, Richard; Elias, Rosalind; Maero, Philip; Leinsdorf, Erich; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2840
        - Bells and Whistles, 1986; SR-25974; Proffitt, K.K.; Pica Records (Box 5)
          PRKP-11687
        - ine Kleine Nachtmusik, (Serenade, K. 525) / Symphony No. 40 In G Minor, (K. 550), 1956; SR-26228; Prohaska, Felix; Vienna State Opera Orchestra, The; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 45)
          SRV-102
        - The Ballet Of Romeo And Juliet, Undated; SR-26090-26091; Prokofiev, Sergei; Rozhdestvensky, Gennadi; Bolshoi Theatre Orchestra; Westminster (Box 12)
          XWN 2206
        - Highlights From La Bohème, 1952; SR-26125; Puccini, Giacomo; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LM 1709
        - Licia Albanese In Highlights From Puccini's Madame Butterfly With James Melton And Other Operatic Arias, 1954; SR-26126; Puccini, Giacomo; Albanese, Licia; Melton, James; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LM-1839
        - Eakins; Elegia, Mitsyn Music; Electronic Study No. 2, Metagrama, 1974; SR-25975; Randall, J.K.; Ceely, Robert; Del Monaco, Alfredo; Composers Recordings, Inc. (Box 5)
          CRI SD 328
        - Computer Music, 1970; SR-25976; Randall, J.K.; Vercoe, Barry; Dodge, Charles; Nonesuch Records (Box 5)
          H-71245
        - Rome Revisited, 1962; SR-26127; Ray Charles Singers, The; Command Records; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 19)
          RS 839 SD
        - Live/Electric Music, 1968; SR-25978; Reich, Steve; Columbia Records (Box 5)
          MS 7265
        - Music for 18 Musicians, 1978; SR-25977; Reich, Steve; ECM Records (Box 5)
          ECM 1-1129
        - The Desert Music, 1985; SR-25979; Reich, Steve; Nonesuch Records (Box 5)
          9 79101-1 F
        - 50th Anniversary Tribute to Nadia Reisenberg, Undated; SR-25980, 25985-25986, 26039-26041; Reisenberg, Nadia; Musical Heritage Society, The (Box 5)
          MHS 7005-6-7-8-9-10
        - First Philadelphia Computer Music Festival, 1979; SR-25981; Richman, Mel; Weisbecker, Joe; Van der Wal, Gooitzen; Modia, Andrew; Ridges, John; Wright, Malcolm; North, Steve; Chamberlain, Hal; Ahl, David; Schertz, Donald; Siegel, Dorothy; Van Lenten, D.H.; Creative Computing (Box 5)
          CR101
        - The Wizard of Oz, 1985; SR-26278; Riemann, Kurt W.; Nightwork Records (Box 46)
          KRTWOAB85
        - In C, 1968; SR-25982; Riley, Terry; Columbia Records (Box 5)
          MS 7178
        - Electronic Music: From Razor Blades To Moog, 1970; SR-26279; Robb, John Donald; Asch Records (Box 46)
          AHS 3438
        - Requiem, 1985; SR-25983; Robb, John Donald; Opus One (Box 5)
          Number 114
        - String Quartet No. 3, 1973; SR-25984; Rochberg, George; Concord String Quartet, The; Nonesuch Records (Box 5)
          H-71283
        - Theremin, 1977; SR-25987; Rockmore, Clara; Delos (Box 6)
          DEL 25437
        - Theremin, 1977; SR-25988; Rockmore, Clara; Delos (Box 6)
        - Theremin, 1977; SR-25989; Rockmore, Clara; Delos (Box 6)
        - Theremin, 1977; SR-25990; Rockmore, Clara; Delos; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 6)
        - Waltzes, 1964; SR-26128; Rubinstein, Artur; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LSC 2726
        - Tchaikovsky Concerto No. 1, 1963; SR-26092; Rubinstein, Artur; Leinsdorf, Erich; Boston Symphony Orchestra, The; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2681
        - Tragoedia, 1968; SR-26162; Rudin, Andrew; Nonesuch Records (Box 44)
          H-71198
        - Tragoedia, 1968; Rudin, Andrew; Nonesuch Records; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 46)
        - Tragoedia, 1968; SR-26280; Rudin, Andrew; Nonesuch Records (Box 46)
        - Tragoedia, 1968; SR-26281; Rudin, Andrew; Nonesuch Records (Box 46)
        - The Nude Paper Sermon, 1969; SR-25991; Salzman, Eric; Nonesuch Records (Box 6)
          H-71231
        - The Nude Paper Sermon, 1969; SR-25992; Salzman, Eric; Nonesuch Records (Box 6)
        - The Velvet Gentleman, 1970; SR-25993; Satie, Eric; London Recordings, Inc. (Box 6)
          DES 18036
        - Toy Planet, 1981; SR-25994; Schmidt, Irmin; Spoerri, Bruno; Spoon Records (Box 6)
          SPOON011
        - Pierrot Lunaire Op.21, 1971; SR-25995; Schoenberg, Arnold; DeGaetani, Jan; Weisberg, Arthur; Nonesuch Records (Box 6)
          H-71251
        - Destruction Of Harmony - The Living Sound Of Synthesizer Based On Bach & Vivaldi, 1971; SR-26282; Schoener, Eberhard; Ariola (Box 46)
          80 847 IU
        - Switched-On Bacharach, 1969; SR-26194; Scott, Christopher; Decca Records (Box 45)
          DL75141
        - Seatrain, 1971; SR-26254-26255 (Box 46)
          EST 659 F1; test pressing.
        - String Quartet / String Quartet No. 5 / String Quartet No. 2, 1973; SR-25996; Seeger, Ruth Crawford; Perle, George; Babbitt, Milton; Composers Quartet, The; Nonesuch Records (Box 6)
          H-71280
        - Bellini and Donizetti Heroines, 1968; SR-25997; Sills, Beverly; ABC Records (Box 6)
          WST-17143
        - The Graduate, 1968; SR-25998; Simon and Garfunkel; Grusin, David; Columbia Records (Box 6)
          OS 3180
        - The Expanding Universe, 1980; SR-25999; Spiegel, Laurie; Philo Records (Box 6)
          PH9003
        - Voice of Taurus, 1978; SR-26260; Spoerri, Bruno; Gold Records (Box 46)
          LP 11061
        - Humoresque (Isaac Stern Plays Great Violin Favorites), 1965; SR-26000; Stern, Isaac; Columbia Records (Box 6)
          ML 6225
        - Nocturnes, Undated; SR-26129; Stokowski, Leopold, and His Symphony Orchestra; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LM 1154
        - Johann and Josef Strauss Waltzes and Polkas, 1982; SR-26001; Strauss, Eduard, and His Orchestra; Vox (Box 6)
          STPL 512.47
        - Sidewinder, 1971; SR-26003; Subotnick, Morton; Columbia Records (Box 6)
          M 30683
        - Touch, 1969; SR-26004; Subotnick, Morton; Columbia Records (Box 6)
          MS 7316
        - The Wild Bull, 1968; SR-26002; Subotnick, Morton; Nonesuch Records (Box 6)
          H-71208
        - Nothing Is..., 1966; SR-26238; Sun Ra; ESP Disk (Box 46)
          ESP-DISKÂ´ 1045
        - My Brother the Wind, 1970; SR-26261; Sun Ra and His Astro Infinity Arkestra; Saturn Research (Box 46)
          ESR521
        - Album II, 1975; SR-26187; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 45)
          1002
        - Album II, 1975; SR-26234; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 45)
        - Album II, 1975; SR-26235; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 45)
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26184; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 44)
          1001
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26185; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 44)
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26186; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 45)
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26232; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 45)
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26233; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 45)
        - Pulaski Skyway, 1972; SR-26262; Swansen, Chris; Badger Records (Box 46)
        - Crazy Horse, 1981; SR-26236; Swansen, Chris; Woods, Phil; Sea Breeze Jazz (Box 45)
          SB 2008
        - Bizet's Carmen (Excerpts), 1946; SR-26005; Swarthout, Gladys; RCA Victor (Box 6)
          LM 1007
        - Audion, 1981; SR-26197; Synergy; Passport Records, Inc. (Box 45)
          PB 6005
        - Electronic Realizations for Rock Orchestra, 1975; SR-26196; Synergy; Passport Records, Inc. (Box 45)
          7167-98009 H
        - Syrinx, 1970; SR-26239; True North Records (Box 46)
          TN-2
        - 777, 1993; SR-26006; System 7; Weird And Unconventional Records (Box 6)
          BFLLP1
        - Phaedra, 1974; SR-26199; Tangerine Dream; Virgin Records (Box 45)
          VR 13-108
        - Good Morning Starshine, 1969; SR-26193; Tartaglia; Capitol Records (Box 45)
          ST-280
        - Tartaglian Theorem, 1968; SR-26007; Tartaglia, John Andrews; Capitol Records (Box 6)
          ST 166
        - Taylor-Made Moog, Undated; SR-26181; Taylor, Larry; Cozy Records (Box 44)
          PL 1008
        - Electric Flowers, 1982; SR-26008; Tcherepnin, Ivan; Composers Recordings, Inc. (Box 6)
          CRI SD 467
        - The Music Improvisation Company, 1970; SR-26142; ECM Records (Box 44)
          ECM 1005 ST
        - Forces, 1983; SR-26130; Thomas, Terence; Fair, Robert; Interface Records (Box 19)
          303065X
        - Hawaiian Luau Party, 1967; SR-26131; Tiny and His Hawaiian Bubbles; Tifton International (Box 19)
          TS 61
        - Snowflakes are Dancing, 1974; SR-26163; Tomita, Isao; RCA Records (Box 44)
          ARL1-0488
        - Snowflakes are Dancing, 1974; SR-26202; Tomita, Isao; RCA Records (Box 45)
        - Zero Time, 1971; SR-26179; Tonto's Expanding Head Band; Embryo Records (Box 44)
          SD 732
        - Nutcracker Suite / The Skaters Waltz / William Tell: Overture, 1956; SR-26132; Toscanini, Arturo; NBC Symphony Orchestra; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LM 1986
        - Country Moog: Switched on Nashville, 1972; SR-26167; Trythall, Gil; Athena Records (Box 44)
          Stereo 6003
        - Nashville Gold: Switched on Moog, 1973; SR-26180; Trythall, Gil; Athena Records (Box 44)
          Stereo 6004
        - Nashville Gold: Switched on Moog, 1973; SR-26400; Trythall, Gil; Athena Records (Box 71)